[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the viceroy for the Trade Federation in the Star wars saga?", "correct_answer": "Nute Gunray", "incorrect_answers": ["Rune Haako", "passel Argente", "Poggle the Lesser"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these cooking methods does not involve hot oil or fat?", "correct_answer": "Boiling", "incorrect_answers": ["Stir Frying", "Pan Frying", "Sauteing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This contractile tissue of the body is the subject of study of myology.", "correct_answer": "muscles", "incorrect_answers": ["blood cells", "bones", "hairs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "David Suchet and Peter Ustinov are two actors who have played the role of the famous detective Sherlock Holmes.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All of the following are fruits except which one?", "correct_answer": "corn", "incorrect_answers": ["orange", "cherry", "apple"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What term is commonly used to denote a group of foxes?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Earth", "Troop", "Skulk"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the full name of Rocky, portrayed by Sylvester Stallone in the Rocky movies?", "correct_answer": "Robert Balboa, Sr.", "incorrect_answers": ["Raul Balboa, Sr.", "Riccardo Balboa, Sr.", "Romano Balboa, Sr."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What term is commonly used to refer to the young of the guinea pig?", "correct_answer": "Pups", "incorrect_answers": ["Kits", "Calves", "Piglets"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the gestation period for an aardvark?", "correct_answer": "7 months", "incorrect_answers": ["1 full year", "9 months", "3 months"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "People suffering from graphophobia are afraid of what?", "correct_answer": "Writing", "incorrect_answers": ["Hair", "Speaking", "Animals"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How do Peter and his team defeat the White Bitch in the parody Epic Movie?", "correct_answer": "Peter finds a remote that lets him stop time.", "incorrect_answers": ["They defeat the army.", "They lure her in a trap.", "They bring Harry Potter along and he kills everyone."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What were the names of the men that attempted to rob the bank in the movie Dog Day Afternoon?", "correct_answer": "Sonny and Sal", "incorrect_answers": ["Sonny and Mickey", "Sam and Sal", "Bonnie and Clyde"]}]